A Guide to the Confederate Pension Records, 1884-1978
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Certificates, 1908-1974., Extent: 39 boxes. (Box 27-66.)
  - Subseries A: Allowed, 1925-1974., Extent: 38 boxes. (Box 27-65.)
    - Sub Subseries 2: Soldiers, 1925-1958, 16 boxes. (Box 28-44)
      - 1925
        - Warren County (Box 32, Folder 12)
        - Warwick County (Box 32, Folder 13)
        - Washington County (Box 32, Folder 14)
        - Westmoreland County (Box 32, Folder 15)
        - Wise County (Box 32, Folder 16)
        - Wythe County (Box 32, Folder 17)
        - York County (Box 32, Folder 18)
        - Alexandria (Box 33, Folder 1)
        - Bristol (Box 33, Folder 2)
        - Buena Vista (Box 33, Folder 3)
        - Charlottesville (Box 33, Folder 4)
        - Clifton Forge (Box 33, Folder 5)
        - Danville (Box 33, Folder 6)
        - Fredericksburg (Box 33, Folder 7)
        - Lynchburg (Box 33, Folder 8)
        - Newport News (Box 33, Folder 9)
        - Norfolk (Box 33, Folder 10)
        - Petersburg (Box 33, Folder 11)
        - Portsmouth (Box 33, Folder 12)
        - Radford (Box 33, Folder 13)
        - Richmond (Box 33, Folder 14)
        - Roanoke (Box 33, Folder 15)
        - Staunton (Box 33, Folder 16)
        - Winchester (Box 33, Folder 17)
        - Washington, D.C. (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - 1927
        - Accomack County (Box 33, Folder 19)
        - Albemarle County (Box 33, Folder 20)
        - Alleghany County (Box 33, Folder 21)
        - Amelia County (Box 33, Folder 22)
        - Amherst County (Box 33, Folder 23)
        - Appomattox County (Box 33, Folder 24)
        - Arlington County (Box 33, Folder 25)
        - Augusta County (Box 33, Folder 26)
        - Bath County (Box 33, Folder 27)
        - Bedford County (Box 33, Folder 28)
        - Bland County (Box 33, Folder 29)
        - Botetourt County (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - Brunswick County (Box 34, Folder 2)
        - Buchanan County (Box 34, Folder 3)
        - Buckingham County (Box 34, Folder 4)
        - Campbell County (Box 34, Folder 5)
        - Caroline County (Box 34, Folder 6)
        - Carroll County (Box 34, Folder 7)
        - Charles City County (Box 34, Folder 8)
        - Charlotte County (Box 34, Folder 9)
        - Chesterfield County (Box 34, Folder 10)
        - Clarke County (Box 34, Folder 11)
        - Craig County (Box 34, Folder 12)
        - Culpeper County (Box 34, Folder 13)
        - Cumberland County (Box 34, Folder 14)
        - Dickenson County (Box 34, Folder 15)
        - Dinwiddie County (Box 34, Folder 16)
        - Elizabeth City County (Box 34, Folder 17)
        - Essex County (Box 34, Folder 18)
        - Fairfax County (Box 34, Folder 19)
        - Fauquier County (Box 34, Folder 20)
        - Floyd County (Box 34, Folder 21)
        - Fluvanna County (Box 34, Folder 22)
        - No Box 35
        - Franklin County (Box 36, Folder 1)
        - Frederick County (Box 36, Folder 2)
        - Giles County (Box 36, Folder 3)
        - Gloucester County (Box 36, Folder 4)
        - Goochland County (Box 36, Folder 5)
        - Grayson County (Box 36, Folder 6)
        - Greene County (Box 36, Folder 7)
        - Greensville County (Box 36, Folder 8)
        - Halifax County (Box 36, Folder 9)
        - Hanover County (Box 36, Folder 10)
        - Henry County (Box 36, Folder 11)
        - Henrico County (Box 36, Folder 12)
        - Highland County (Box 36, Folder 13)
        - Isle of Wight County (Box 36, Folder 14)
        - James City County (Box 36, Folder 15)
        - King & Queen County (Box 36, Folder 16)
        - King George County (Box 36, Folder 17)
        - King William County (Box 36, Folder 18)
        - Lancaster County (Box 36, Folder 19)
        - Lee County (Box 36, Folder 20)
        - Loudoun County (Box 36, Folder 21)
        - Louisa County (Box 36, Folder 22)
        - Lunenburg County (Box 36, Folder 23)
        - Madison County (Box 37, Folder 1)
        - Mathews County (Box 37, Folder 2)
        - Mecklenburg County (Box 37, Folder 3)
        - Middlesex County (Box 37, Folder 4)
        - Montgomery County (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - Nansemond County (Box 37, Folder 6)
        - Nelson County (Box 37, Folder 7)
        - New Kent County (Box 37, Folder 8)
        - Norfolk County (Box 37, Folder 9)
        - Northampton County (Box 37, Folder 10)
        - Northumberland County (Box 37, Folder 11)
        - Nottoway County (Box 37, Folder 12)
        - Orange County (Box 37, Folder 13)
        - Page County (Box 37, Folder 14)
        - Patrick County (Box 37, Folder 15)
        - Pittsylvania County (Box 37, Folder 16)
        - Powhatan County (Box 37, Folder 17)
        - Prince Edward County (Box 37, Folder 18)
        - Prince George County (Box 37, Folder 19)
        - Prince William County (Box 37, Folder 20)
        - Princess Anne County (Box 37, Folder 21)
        - Pulaski County (Box 37, Folder 22)
        - Rappahannock County (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - Richmond County (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - Roanoke County (Box 38, Folder 3)
        - Rockbridge County (Box 38, Folder 4)
        - Rockingham County (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - Russell County (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - Scott County (Box 38, Folder 7)
        - Shenandoah County (Box 38, Folder 8)
        - Smyth County (Box 38, Folder 9)
        - Southampton County (Box 38, Folder 10)
        - Spotsylvania County (Box 38, Folder 11)
        - Stafford County (Box 38, Folder 12)
        - Surry County (Box 38, Folder 13)
        - Sussex County (Box 38, Folder 14)
        - Tazewell County (Box 38, Folder 15)
        - Warren County (Box 38, Folder 16)
        - Warwick County (Box 38, Folder 17)
        - Washington County (Box 38, Folder 18)
        - Westmoreland County (Box 38, Folder 19)
        - Wise County (Box 39, Folder 1)
        - Wythe County (Box 39, Folder 2)
        - York County (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - Alexandria (Box 39, Folder 4)
        - Bristol (Box 39, Folder 5)
        - Buena Vista (Box 39, Folder 6)
        - Charlottesville (Box 39, Folder 7)
        - Clifton Forge (Box 39, Folder 8)
        - Danville (Box 39, Folder 9)
        - Fredericksburg (Box 39, Folder 10)
        - Lynchburg (Box 39, Folder 11)
        - Newport News (Box 39, Folder 12)
        - Norfolk (Box 39, Folder 13)
        - Petersburg (Box 39, Folder 14)
        - Portsmouth (Box 39, Folder 15)
        - Radford (Box 39, Folder 16)
        - Richmond (Box 39, Folder 17)
        - Roanoke (Box 39, Folder 18)
        - Staunton (Box 39, Folder 19)
        - Williamsburg (Box 39, Folder 20)
        - Winchester (Box 39, Folder 21)
        - Washington, D.C. (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - 1928
        - Accomack County (Box 39, Folder 23)
        - Albemarle County (Box 39, Folder 24)
        - Alleghany County (Box 39, Folder 25)
        - Amelia County (Box 39, Folder 26)
        - Amherst County (Box 39, Folder 27)
        - Appomattox County (Box 39, Folder 28)
        - Arlington County (Box 39, Folder 29)
        - Augusta County (Box 40, Folder 1)
        - Bath County (Box 40, Folder 2)
        - Bedford County (Box 40, Folder 3)
        - Bland County (Box 40, Folder 4)
        - Botetourt County (Box 40, Folder 5)
        - Brunswick County (Box 40, Folder 6)
        - Buchanan County (Box 40, Folder 7)
        - Buckingham County (Box 40, Folder 8)
        - Campbell County (Box 40, Folder 9)
        - Caroline County (Box 40, Folder 10)
        - Carroll County (Box 40, Folder 11)
        - Charles City County (Box 40, Folder 12)
        - Charlotte County (Box 40, Folder 13)
        - Chesterfield County (Box 40, Folder 14)
        - Clarke County (Box 40, Folder 15)
        - Craig County (Box 40, Folder 16)
        - Culpeper County (Box 40, Folder 17)
        - Cumberland County (Box 40, Folder 18)
        - Dickenson County (Box 40, Folder 19)
        - Dinwiddie County (Box 40, Folder 20)
        - Elizabeth City County (Box 40, Folder 21)
        - Essex County (Box 40, Folder 22)
        - Fairfax County (Box 40, Folder 23)
        - Fauquier County (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - Floyd County (Box 41, Folder 2)
        - Fluvanna County (Box 41, Folder 3)
        - Franklin County (Box 41, Folder 4)
        - Frederick County (Box 41, Folder 5)
        - Giles County (Box 41, Folder 6)
        - Gloucester County (Box 41, Folder 7)
        - Goochland County (Box 41, Folder 8)
        - Grayson County (Box 41, Folder 9)
        - Greene County (Box 41, Folder 10)
        - Greensville County (Box 41, Folder 11)
        - Halifax County (Box 41, Folder 12)
        - Hanover County (Box 41, Folder 13)
        - Henrico County (Box 41, Folder 14)
        - Henry County (Box 41, Folder 15)
        - Highland County (Box 41, Folder 16)
        - Isle of Wight County (Box 41, Folder 17)
        - James City County (Box 41, Folder 18)
        - King & Queen County (Box 41, Folder 19)
        - King George County (Box 41, Folder 20)
        - King William County (Box 41, Folder 21)
        - Lancaster County (Box 41, Folder 22)
        - Lee County (Box 42, Folder 1)
        - Loudoun County (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - Louisa County (Box 42, Folder 3)
        - Lunenburg County (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - Madison County (Box 42, Folder 5)
        - Mathews County (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - Mecklenburg County (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Middlesex County (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - Montgomery County (Box 42, Folder 9)
        - Nansemond County (Box 42, Folder 10)
        - Nelson County (Box 42, Folder 11)
        - New Kent County (Box 42, Folder 12)
        - Norfolk County (Box 42, Folder 13)
        - Northampton County (Box 42, Folder 14)
        - Northumberland County (Box 42, Folder 15)
        - Nottoway County (Box 42, Folder 16)
        - Orange County (Box 42, Folder 17)
        - Page County (Box 42, Folder 18)
        - Patrick County (Box 42, Folder 19)
        - Pittsylvania County (Box 42, Folder 20)
        - Powhatan County (Box 42, Folder 21)
        - Prince Edward County (Box 42, Folder 22)
        - Prince George County (Box 42, Folder 23)
        - Prince William County (Box 42, Folder 24)
        - Princess Anne County (Box 42, Folder 25)
        - Pulaski County (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - Rappahannock County (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - Richmond County (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - Roanoke County (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - Rockbridge County (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - Rockingham County (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - Russell County (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - Scott County (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - Shenandoah County (Box 43, Folder 9)
        - Smyth County (Box 43, Folder 10)
        - Southampton County (Box 43, Folder 11)
        - Spotsylvania County (Box 43, Folder 12)
        - Stafford County (Box 43, Folder 13)
        - Surry County (Box 43, Folder 14)
        - Sussex County (Box 43, Folder 15)
        - Tazewell County (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - Warren County (Box 43, Folder 17)
        - Warwick County (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - Washington County (Box 43, Folder 19)
        - Westmoreland County (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - Wise County (Box 43, Folder 21)
        - Wythe County (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - York County (Box 43, Folder 23)
        - Alexandria (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - Bristol (Box 44, Folder 2)
        - Buena Vista (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - Charlottesville (Box 44, Folder 4)
        - Clifton Forge (Box 44, Folder 5)
        - Danville (Box 44, Folder 6)
        - Fredericksburg (Box 44, Folder 7)
        - Hopewell (Box 44, Folder 8)
        - Lynchburg (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - Newport News (Box 44, Folder 10)
        - Norfolk (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - Petersburg (Box 44, Folder 12)
        - Portsmouth (Box 44, Folder 13)
        - Radford (Box 44, Folder 14)
        - Richmond (Box 44, Folder 15)
        - Roanoke (Box 44, Folder 16)
        - Staunton (Box 44, Folder 17)
        - Williamsburg (Box 44, Folder 18)
        - Winchester (Box 44, Folder 19)
        - Washington, D.C. (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - 1949-1958 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Sub Subseries 3: Widows, 1927-1974, 22 boxes. (Box 45-65)
      The Widow's Certificates sub subseries is housed in twenty-two archival boxes and is arranged chronologically, then alphabetically by locality and pensioner. Certificates between 1969 and 1974 are arranged chronologically, then alphabetical by pensioner. These certificates contain similar information included on the soldier's certificates. Note that these certificates do not include the name of the veteran. Blind pensioners and pensioners who died are marked accordingly on the certificate.
      - 1927
        - Accomack County (Box 45, Folder 1)
        - Albemarle County (Box 45, Folder 2)
        - Alleghany County (Box 45, Folder 3)
        - Amelia County (Box 45, Folder 4)
        - Amherst County (Box 45, Folder 5)
        - Appomattox County (Box 45, Folder 6)
        - Arlington County (Box 45, Folder 7)
        - Augusta County (Box 45, Folder 8)
        - Bath County (Box 45, Folder 9)
        - Bedford County (Box 45, Folder 10)
        - Bland County (Box 45, Folder 11)
        - Botetourt County (Box 45, Folder 12)
        - Brunswick County (Box 45, Folder 13)
        - Buchanan County (Box 45, Folder 14)
        - Buckingham County (Box 45, Folder 15)
        - Campbell County (Box 45, Folder 16)
        - Caroline County (Box 46, Folder 1)
        - Carroll County (Box 46, Folder 2)
        - Charles City County (Box 46, Folder 3)
        - Charlotte County (Box 46, Folder 4)
        - Chesterfield County (Box 46, Folder 5)
        - Clarke County (Box 46, Folder 6)
        - Craig County (Box 46, Folder 7)
        - Culpeper County (Box 46, Folder 8)
        - Cumberland County (Box 46, Folder 9)
        - Dickenson County (Box 46, Folder 10)
        - Dinwiddie County (Box 46, Folder 11)
        - Elizabeth City County (Box 46, Folder 12)
        - Essex County (Box 46, Folder 13)
        - Fairfax County (Box 46, Folder 14)
        - Fauquier County (Box 46, Folder 15)
        - Floyd County (Box 46, Folder 16)
        - Fluvanna County (Box 46, Folder 17)
        - Franklin County (Box 47, Folder 1)
        - Frederick County (Box 47, Folder 2)
        - Giles County (Box 47, Folder 3)
        - Gloucester County (Box 47, Folder 4)
        - Goochland County (Box 47, Folder 5)
        - Grayson County (Box 47, Folder 6)
        - Greene County (Box 47, Folder 7)
        - Greensville County (Box 47, Folder 8)
        - Halifax County (Box 47, Folder 9)
        - Hanover County (Box 47, Folder 10)
        - Henrico County (Box 47, Folder 11)
        - Henry County (Box 47, Folder 12)
        - Highland County (Box 47, Folder 13)
        - Isle of Wight County (Box 47, Folder 14)
        - James City County (Box 47, Folder 15)
        - King & Queen County (Box 47, Folder 16)
        - King George County (Box 47, Folder 17)
        - King William County (Box 47, Folder 18)
        - Lancaster County (Box 48, Folder 1)
        - Lee County (Box 48, Folder 2)
        - Loudoun County (Box 48, Folder 3)
        - Louisa County (Box 48, Folder 4)
        - Lunenburg County (Box 48, Folder 5)
        - Madison County (Box 48, Folder 6)
        - Mathews County (Box 48, Folder 7)
        - Mecklenburg County (Box 48, Folder 8)
        - Middlesex County (Box 48, Folder 9)
        - Montgomery County (Box 48, Folder 10)
        - Nansemond County (Box 48, Folder 11)
        - Nelson County (Box 48, Folder 12)
        - New Kent County (Box 48, Folder 13)
        - Norfolk County (Box 48, Folder 14)
        - Northampton County (Box 48, Folder 15)
        - Northumberland County (Box 48, Folder 16)
        - Nottoway County (Box 48, Folder 17)
        - Orange County (Box 48, Folder 18)
        - Page County (Box 48, Folder 19)
        - Patrick County (Box 48, Folder 20)
        - Pittsylvania County (Box 49, Folder 1)
        - Powhatan County (Box 49, Folder 2)
        - Prince Edward County (Box 49, Folder 3)
        - Prince George County (Box 49, Folder 4)
        - Prince William County (Box 49, Folder 5)
        - Princess Anne County (Box 49, Folder 6)
        - Pulaski County (Box 49, Folder 7)
        - Rappahannock County (Box 49, Folder 8)
        - Richmond County (Box 49, Folder 9)
        - Roanoke County (Box 49, Folder 10)
        - Rockbridge County (Box 49, Folder 11)
        - Rockingham County (Box 49, Folder 12)
        - Russell County (Box 49, Folder 13)
        - Scott County (Box 49, Folder 14)
        - Shenandoah County (Box 49, Folder 15)
        - Smyth County (Box 50, Folder 1)
        - Southampton County (Box 50, Folder 2)
        - Spotsylvania County (Box 50, Folder 3)
        - Stafford County (Box 50, Folder 4)
        - Surry County (Box 50, Folder 5)
        - Sussex County (Box 50, Folder 6)
        - Tazewell County (Box 50, Folder 7)
        - Warren County (Box 50, Folder 8)
        - Warwick County (Box 50, Folder 9)
        - Washington County (Box 50, Folder 10)
        - Westmoreland County (Box 50, Folder 11)
        - Wise County (Box 50, Folder 12)
        - Wythe County (Box 50, Folder 13)
        - York County (Box 50, Folder 14)
        - Alexandria (Box 50, Folder 15)
        - Bristol (Box 50, Folder 16)
        - Buena Vista (Box 50, Folder 17)
        - Charlottesville (Box 50, Folder 18)
        - Clifton Forge (Box 50, Folder 19)
        - Danville (Box 50, Folder 20)
        - Fredericksburg (Box 50, Folder 21)
        - Hopewell (Box 50, Folder 22)
        - Lynchburg (Box 50, Folder 23)
        - Newport News (Box 50, Folder 24)
        - Norfolk (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - Petersburg (Box 51, Folder 2)
        - Portsmouth (Box 51, Folder 3)
        - Radford (Box 51, Folder 4)
        - Richmond
          - A-F (Box 51, Folder 5)
          - G-M (Box 51, Folder 6)
          - N-S (Box 51, Folder 7)
          - T-Z (Box 51, Folder 8)
        - Roanoke (Box 51, Folder 9)
        - Staunton (Box 52, Folder 1)
        - Williamsburg (Box 52, Folder 2)
        - Winchester (Box 52, Folder 3)
        - Washington, D.C. (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - 1928
        - Accomack County (Box 52, Folder 5)
        - Albemarle County (Box 52, Folder 6)
        - Alleghany County (Box 52, Folder 7)
        - Amelia County (Box 52, Folder 8)
        - Amherst County (Box 52, Folder 9)
        - Appomattox County (Box 52, Folder 10)
        - Arlington County (Box 52, Folder 19)
        - Augusta County (Box 52, Folder 12)
        - Bath County (Box 52, Folder 13)
        - Bedford County (Box 52, Folder 14)
        - Bland County (Box 53, Folder 1)
        - Botetourt County (Box 53, Folder 2)
        - Brunswick County (Box 53, Folder 3)
        - Buchanan County (Box 53, Folder 4)
        - Buckingham County (Box 53, Folder 5)
        - Campbell County (Box 53, Folder 6)
        - Caroline County (Box 53, Folder 7)
        - Carroll County (Box 53, Folder 8)
        - Charles City County (Box 53, Folder 9)
        - Charlotte County (Box 53, Folder 10)
        - Chesterfield County (Box 53, Folder 11)
        - Clarke County (Box 53, Folder 12)
        - Craig County (Box 53, Folder 13)
        - Culpeper County (Box 53, Folder 14)
        - Cumberland County (Box 53, Folder 15)
        - Dickenson County (Box 53, Folder 16)
        - Dinwiddie County (Box 53, Folder 17)
        - Elizabeth City County (Box 54, Folder 1)
        - Essex County (Box 54, Folder 2)
        - Fairfax County (Box 54, Folder 3)
        - Fauquier County (Box 54, Folder 4)
        - Floyd County (Box 54, Folder 5)
        - Fluvanna County (Box 54, Folder 6)
        - Franklin County (Box 54, Folder 7)
        - Frederick County (Box 54, Folder 8)
        - Giles County (Box 54, Folder 9)
        - Gloucester County (Box 54, Folder 10)
        - Goochland County (Box 54, Folder 11)
        - Grayson County (Box 54, Folder 12)
        - Greene County (Box 54, Folder 13)
        - Greensville County (Box 54, Folder 14)
        - Halifax County (Box 55, Folder 1)
        - Hanover County (Box 55, Folder 2)
        - Henrico County (Box 55, Folder 3)
        - Henry County (Box 55, Folder 4)
        - Highland County (Box 55, Folder 5)
        - Isle of Wight County (Box 55, Folder 6)
        - James City County (Box 55, Folder 7)
        - King & Queen County (Box 55, Folder 8)
        - King George County (Box 55, Folder 9)
        - King William County (Box 55, Folder 10)
        - Lancaster County (Box 55, Folder 11)
        - Lee County (Box 55, Folder 12)
        - Loudoun County (Box 55, Folder 13)
        - Louisa County (Box 55, Folder 14)
        - Lunenburg County (Box 55, Folder 15)
        - Madison County (Box 56, Folder 1)
        - Mathews County (Box 56, Folder 2)
        - Mecklenburg County (Box 56, Folder 3)
        - Middlesex County (Box 56, Folder 4)
        - Montgomery County (Box 56, Folder 5)
        - Nansemond County (Box 56, Folder 6)
        - Nelson County (Box 56, Folder 7)
        - New Kent County (Box 56, Folder 8)
        - Norfolk County (Box 56, Folder 9)
        - Northampton County (Box 56, Folder 10)
        - Northumberland County (Box 56, Folder 11)
        - Nottoway County (Box 56, Folder 12)
        - Orange County (Box 56, Folder 13)
        - Page County (Box 56, Folder 14)
        - Patrick County (Box 56, Folder 15)
        - Pittsylvania County (Box 56, Folder 16)
        - Powhatan County (Box 56, Folder 17)
        - Prince Edward County (Box 57, Folder 1)
        - Prince George County (Box 57, Folder 2)
        - Prince William County (Box 57, Folder 3)
        - Princess Anne County (Box 57, Folder 4)
        - Pulaski County (Box 57, Folder 5)
        - Rappahannock County (Box 57, Folder 6)
        - Richmond County (Box 57, Folder 7)
        - Roanoke County (Box 57, Folder 8)
        - Rockbridge County (Box 57, Folder 9)
        - Rockingham County (Box 57, Folder 10)
        - Russell County (Box 57, Folder 11)
        - Scott County (Box 57, Folder 12)
        - Shenandoah County (Box 57, Folder 13)
        - Smyth County (Box 57, Folder 14)
        - Southampton County (Box 58, Folder 1)
        - Spotsylvania County (Box 58, Folder 2)
        - Stafford County (Box 58, Folder 3)
        - Surry County (Box 58, Folder 4)
        - Sussex County (Box 58, Folder 5)
        - Tazewell County (Box 58, Folder 6)
        - Warren County (Box 58, Folder 7)
        - Warwick County (Box 58, Folder 8)
        - Washington County (Box 58, Folder 9)
        - Westmoreland County (Box 58, Folder 10)
        - Wise County (Box 58, Folder 11)
        - Wythe County (Box 58, Folder 12)
        - York County (Box 58, Folder 13)
        - Alexandria (Box 58, Folder 14)
        - Bristol (Box 58, Folder 15)
        - Buena Vista (Box 58, Folder 16)
        - Charlottesville (Box 58, Folder 17)
        - Clifton Forge (Box 58, Folder 18)
        - Danville (Box 58, Folder 19)
        - Fredericksburg (Box 58, Folder 20)
        - Hopewell (Box 58, Folder 21)
        - Lynchburg (Box 58, Folder 22)
        - Newport News (Box 59, Folder 1)
        - Norfolk (Box 59, Folder 2)
        - Petersburg (Box 59, Folder 3)
        - Portsmouth (Box 59, Folder 4)
        - Radford (Box 59, Folder 5)
        - Richmond
          - A-F (Box 59, Folder 6)
          - G-M (Box 59, Folder 7)
          - N-Y (Box 59, Folder 8)
        - Roanoke
          - A-M (Box 60, Folder 1)
          - N-W (Box 60, Folder 2)
        - Staunton (Box 60, Folder 3)
        - Williamsburg (Box 60, Folder 4)
        - Winchester (Box 60, Folder 5)
        - Washington, D.C. (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - 1949
        - Accomack-Cumberland (Box 60, Folder 7)
        - Dickenson-Lunenburg (Box 60, Folder 8)
        - Madison-Pulaski (Box 60, Folder 9)